<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Externals on</title><link>https://commet-wiki.github.io/external/</link><description>Recent content in Externals on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 19:33:06 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://commet-wiki.github.io/external/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Featured Torrents</title><link>https://commet-wiki.github.io/external/groups/fcem/torrents/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 19:33:06 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://commet-wiki.github.io/external/groups/fcem/torrents/</guid><description>
CAT #
Literally anything that catindian has uploaded CAT and other MBA entrance exam test series CAT MBA Study Materials DILR 1000 by Career Launcher Elites Grid LRDI 2022 CAT MBA VARC 1000 2023 Module 1 and 2 Module 3 and 4 Module 5 and module 6 QA 1000 by CL Part 1 (It&amp;rsquo;s a three part torrent) Arithmetic for CAT by Ravi Prakash 2023 QA 1000 by CL Part 2 QA 1000 by CL Part 3 (Contains 2022 TIME materials, 2022 VARC 1000 CADs as well) Some CAT stuff from 2022 and before (Not a torrent, one drive link)</description></item><item><title>Rules</title><link>https://commet-wiki.github.io/external/groups/fcem/rules/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 16:59:49 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://commet-wiki.github.io/external/groups/fcem/rules/</guid><description>Selling is forbidden
You are not allowed to share any type of content for the exchange of money or anything equivalent to it. This will get you banned instantly, without any warning. The buyer won&amp;rsquo;t be punished, though.
Respect the privacy of other members
Doxxing any member of the community will not be tolerated. You are supposed to respect everyone&amp;rsquo;s privacy. Not following this rule will obviously get you banned without a warning.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://commet-wiki.github.io/external/groups/fcem/about/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 16:46:44 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://commet-wiki.github.io/external/groups/fcem/about/</guid><description>FCEM is a telegram community dedicated to sharing educational materials for free using the power of torrents
Group links
Telegram Channel (last updated 26th Sep 2023)
Telegram Group
If you are new to torrenting, you can always follow the official COMMET resources and FAQ for any beginner to intermediate level doubts.
Please note that none of the members are responsible for any copyright infringement that might if so ever occur.</description></item></channel></rss>