<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Externals on</title><link>https://commet-wiki.github.io/external/</link><description>Recent content in Externals on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 10:24:33 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://commet-wiki.github.io/external/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Featured communities</title><link>https://commet-wiki.github.io/external/groups/home/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 10:24:33 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://commet-wiki.github.io/external/groups/home/</guid><description>Communities featured by COMMET #
FCEM Get your community featured #
To get featured on this page, join our matrix and ask there. That&amp;rsquo;s it.</description></item><item><title>Featured Torrents</title><link>https://commet-wiki.github.io/external/groups/fcem/torrents/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 19:33:06 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://commet-wiki.github.io/external/groups/fcem/torrents/</guid><description>CAT #
Literally anything that catindian has uploaded CAT and other MBA entrance exam test series CAT MBA Study Materials DILR 1000 by Career Launcher Elites Grid LRDI 2022 CAT MBA CAT 2023 mocks by IMS, TIME and CL VARC 1000 2023 Module 1 and 2 Module 3 and 4 Module 5 and module 6 Strategy and Grammar Lessons NMAT-SNAP Addons QA 1000 by CL Part 1 (It&amp;rsquo;s a three part torrent) QA 1000 by CL Part 2 QA 1000 by CL Part 3 (Contains 2022 TIME materials, 2022 VARC 1000 CADs as well) Some CAT stuff from 2022 and before (Not a torrent, one drive link) EG LRDI 2023 Seating Arrangement Matrix Arrangement Table Charts Truth and Lie, Pipes and Networks Set Theory Entry and Exit Games and Tournament Project Management Selections and Distributions Daily Puzzles for CAT EG QA 2023 Number System Algebra [1] Algebra [2] Algebra [3] Algebra [4] Arithmetic[1] Arithmetic[2] Arithmetic[3] Arithmetic[4] Geometry[1] Geometry[2] Geometry[3] Geometry[4] Geometry[5] Modern Math Set Theory Time, Speed and Distance Comprehensive Course on Number System for CAT 2023 by Ravi Prakash, Unacademy Arithmetic for CAT by Ravi Prakash 2023 PW MBA Pioneer 2023 Batch LRDI CS/IT #
Complete Course on Computer Architecture for GATE, Unacademy GATE CS/IT courses by Sanchit Jain, Unacademy (All subjects excluding the one above) [GeeksForGeeks] Data Structures With Python Bank exams #
Revolution 2023 : Complete Course of Quant for All Bank Exams 2023 by Aashish Arora, Unacademy Part I Part II Part III UDAAN - A complete Course on (Prelim) DI for Bank Exams by Aashish Arora, Unacademy DISHA 2.</description></item><item><title>Rules</title><link>https://commet-wiki.github.io/external/groups/fcem/rules/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 16:59:49 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://commet-wiki.github.io/external/groups/fcem/rules/</guid><description>Selling is forbidden
You are not allowed to share any type of content for the exchange of money or anything equivalent to it. This will get you banned instantly, without any warning. The buyer won&amp;rsquo;t be punished, though.
Respect the privacy of other members
Doxxing any member of the community will not be tolerated. You are supposed to respect everyone&amp;rsquo;s privacy. Not following this rule will obviously get you banned without a warning.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://commet-wiki.github.io/external/groups/fcem/about/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 16:46:44 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://commet-wiki.github.io/external/groups/fcem/about/</guid><description>FCEM is a telegram community dedicated to sharing educational materials for free using the power of torrents
FCEM community links
Telegram Group (main) (last updated 19th of Nov 2023)
Telegram Channel (for updates)
Before joining, please make sure to read the rules. And here's the list of torrents we feature and seed.
If you are new to torrenting, you can always follow the official COMMET resources and FAQ for any beginner to intermediate level doubts.</description></item></channel></rss>